So in this section we're going to take everything we've learned and
在这一部分 我们将运用所有学到的知识
we're going to build our first neural network to train over the datasets that
来构建我们的第一个神经网络 用来训练
we just created.
我们刚刚创建的数据集
Now what I'd like for you to do for
这里 我想让大家做的就是
this project is to start with your neural net form the last chapter.
从上一章做的成果开始搭建神经网络
I guess the last module that you did where you built a basic neural network
我猜大家在上一个模块 已经构建了一个基本神经网络
for predicting on a structured data dataset.
来对结构化的数据集做预测
Then I would like to take this three layer neural network and
现在 我将运用三层神经网络
remove the non-linearity in the hidden layer.
去除隐藏层的非线性
I'll show you why later.
稍后我再说明原因
Then I would like for you to use the functions that we created above
然后 我要大家利用之前创建的函数
to generate the trained data on the fly.
快速生成训练数据
So a review and a label goes in.
也就是 每输入一条评论和一个标签
It's converted into the two vectors that we need for the input and output data.
就会分别转换成我们所需的输入和输出两个向量
And then a forward pass and a back prop pass happen, so
然后通过正向传播和反向传播
that the data is being trained on the fly.
快速训练数据
Next thing I would like for you to do is create a function for
接下来要做的 就是创建一个函数
pre-processing the data.
来预处理数据
So that all of these kind of vocabulary variables, and
这样 让所有这些词汇变量
word2index variables are variables of this class, so
word2index 变量 都在这一类中
everything is self-contained in that class.
这样 这个类本身特征齐全 相对独立
And then modify the train variable to actually train over the entire corpus,
然后 来改进训练变量 通过针对整个语料库进行训练
instead of just on one inputs and targets list.
而不只是针对一组 inputs_list 和 targets_list 来训练
So, that's kind of what I would like for you to do.
所以 这些就是我希望大家做的
You can start with either with this shell,
你可以从这个 shell 开始做
that was presented at the beginning of your last week's chapter or
可在上周的章节开始处找到
with the complete neural net that you started with last time.
或者从你上次所完成的神经网络开始做
Now if you do need help, obviously the first thing to do is to go re-watch
如果你还需要帮助 可以先观看
the previous week's Udacity lectures, make you're familiar with that
之前的优达学城讲座
propagation and it's gradient ascent, and the error measure
熟悉一下反向传播、梯度下降和误差测量
that we're using and also how to modify back prop to get rid of non-linearity.
以及如何修正反向传播来摆脱非线性 这些都是这里会用到的
And if you still need more help, go ahead and
如果还不够的话
check out chapters three through five of Grokking Deep Learning.
你可以查看《Grokking深度学习》 一书的第 3 ~ 5 章
I've included the 40% off code here.
我已经给出了 40% 的代码
It does a comprehensive review of fore prop, back prop and error gradients and
书上全面综述了正向传播、反向传播、误差梯度
stochastic gradient descent.
和随机梯度下降
In a moment I'll show you how I put this network together, and
一会儿 我将向大家展示 我是如何完成这个网络的
then we'll kind of talk about the different changes that we made.
然后 我们也会聊一聊我们所做的一些不同的更改
All right, I'll see you then.
好的 一会儿见